sculpteo.com 2019-11-18

# Personal Information & Data

#### Personal Information & Data

Here you will find information regarding your personal information & data while using Sculpteo’s services. This information is arranged as follows:

  * Shared and Collected Information
  * Modifying or Deleting Your Personal Data
  * Security Measures and Updates

## Shared and Collected Information 

#### Collected Information

Sculpteo retains and applies information regarding the name, email address, and postal address of its customers to better cultivate the online 3D printing service. This information helps to process and receive orders.

As you sign up to Sculpteo, if you check the box “I would like to receive information from Sculpteo”, you accept to recieve our weekly newsletter and other support emails from Sculpteo. You are able to unsubscribe from these emails at any time through the email itself, as applicable CNIL regulations.

#### Shared Information

Sculpteo does not sell nor rent any information to third parties. As orders are carried out, some information will be transferred; this applies notably to address communication between Sculpteo and the shipping agency responsible for the order. 

We may also share your information if we estimate that our divulgence of said information is reasonably justified. Notably in the following situations:

  * To comply with legal, regulatory, judicial, or administrative obligations
  * To detect, avoid or process situations of fraudulent activity, security alerts or technical error
  * To protect Sculpteo, its users and the public from right infringements with respect to legality

## Modifying or Deleting Your Personal Data 

You are able to verify and modify your personal data under [My Account](https://www.sculpteo.com/en/my_account/) at any moment. From there you are able to change your personal information under the [Personal Information](https://www.sculpteo.com/en/accounts/update/) section. There you are able to change your name, address, and other personal information.

To completely erase all personal data from our system, or for any other question concerning your personal data, feel free to contact us via [online form](https://www.sculpteo.com/en/contact/) or by email at [contact@sculpteo.com](mailto:contact@sculpteo.com), with a justification of your identity.

## Security Measures and Updates 

#### Data Security

Multiple security measures offer the necessary protection from from unauthorized access, modification or divulgence of the data in our possession. 

Your bank and credit card information is protected with increased vigilance. Bank card transactions are made through Paybox Services with the security they offer. Payments made through Paypal are directed through their services. Individual bank card information is encrypted through an SSL process to which Sculpteo does not have access. Sculpteo does not act as an intermediate of payment transmissions.

#### Policy Updates Regarding Private Information

Sculpteo reserves the right to change and update its privacy policies. We recommend consulting our site regularly to remain up to date with such changes.

#### Contact Us

Please feel free to contact us with even the smallest question concerning our privacy policy. You are able to do so via [email](mailto:contact@sculpteo.com) or [online contact form](https://www.sculpteo.com/en/contact/)
